Hello Hello Friends Anand Channel But Satyam
Gupta's you can see today
our fitting is standing in front of us, so you must be aware that
recently it had a small accident in
which many parts were damaged,
after that we got the front side
installed, so finally we made the
insurance claim, so
our flame has been passed and all the
product is gone, so now we got all the
parts changed and we will tell you in total
how much time it took to make the insurance
claim and what are the processes involved in
making the insurance claim, you
can also click on whenever you
come across any damage, then watch this video completely, it is going to be a
very interesting video
and if you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then do it
and definitely press the bell icon
so that no one
misses interesting videos and bike updates and today, so let's
watch the video completely, so friends, now you can see that
all the parts are done, finally what
we meant was damage, the handle was damaged
here and the rest of the parts you  You
can see here that
all the fiber parts have been opened here and our radiator was also
damaged, which you can see here, it is
completely damaged, so it must be its
own, it has not been opened yet and yes here
you can see the handle is fitting, it is a
new handle and the old handle has been changed
because it was closed, so you
can see that our handle is being set here as well
and you can see something like this, the position of the radiator
is now completely banked, the liter is
also ah,
hey friend, all these that you are seeing now are fiber
parts, this is the side panel of the tank
and you can see this
codeword on the side, that is anti, in which it is written
and this is the part that seems to be below it,
so all this has been opened and all this has been
changed and as you are looking here, you can
see that the
condition of the back looks quite bad, it looks like the
entire fitting, I will
tell you how much difference we made,
what is the process in getting it repaired from Totally
and how can you make an insurance claim,
so watch the full video  Then it is going to be
clear to you in such a video, it has happened, it has happened, it has happened, so you can
see the puncture,
our new radiator is being installed because the
old radiator was completely
damaged, so brother, what we are
installing right now is our new radiator
and as you can see that you can
see here, we had got this also
in the insurance claim, so we are
changing it as well,
now the entire process will be complete,
after this I will
tell you all the expenses that how much was our total expense
or how much did we have to pay in this and
how much did we get as insurance claim, out of
this,
this side was completely broken as
you can see, so we will install it completely, so
friend, finally
our back is complete and
we have kept it covered, let us show you
how, now we have removed this also, now we are going to
tell you its complete details, it is
exactly like before, it has become perfect, just
like our wife's body was broken as before and it was completely
broken  When I went there, I was feeling very bad, so
our work got done here very quickly,
so now we will ask Bhaiya
who handled the entire process of our insurance,
how much did it cost us, what are the
processes, if you
go to make an insurance claim, then the
in-charge will also tell you in full details
that how much did it cost us in total insurance, how much money did we get for
repairing the bike,
how much did we get in more insurance
and how much did we have to invest in it, so
first of all you tell me how much was our total
expense brother, ₹8500 ₹3 8500
₹3, so out of this, how much did we get for insurance,
you got it in full,
because of this you got it for ₹10,
you had to pay the processing charge
and the flame had to be
paid separately, its 175 rupees, means
like whatever happens in insurance, what happens in
Cameron, like vitamin breakage,
liquid items will not remain intact for you,
so whatever fiber item is there with the
series which is attached to you,
leaving it like this, it is fine
Whatever claim charge we have presented for you is approximately Rs. 250,
it means the SIM is there in all the parts, it is
also different for all the bikes,
if yours goes above 20 thousand
then you have to pay ₹500, that means
if it is below the head then you will have to pay 28 rupees for that, I
mean this claim charge is
taken by the insurance company, you people take it,
this insurance company does it, does it
deduct this much money from us, that is why
we give it in hand, that is why
you people take the insurance friend who means incharge
and it is and like whatever fiber
pass etc., it all comes under hundred percent
fort, what was ours, so the
insurance that you had given us,
what is the interest, it was from Zero Africa Hazir
Devta Grid, if you need a watch, if you find a
problem then you can talk to him, we got all this
work done, otherwise
Shiv Shakti Automobile which is in Giridih,
we had purchased from here, so Bhaiya has
very good support and he completed our work
very quickly  So
as friend you have seen our work has been completed very well
here and it will be done very
soon and if we see then our total
expenditure was approximately 40 ₹70 for
Ladakh, our total expense was
470 kg,
apart from the ancient 425, our total expenditure was 470 kg, that is everything
but insurance claim
etc. and whatever counter-attack expenses there were,
taking all that in, so this was the complete process, if you
want a detailed video on this, how to
do it, how to delete and
upload photos etc., then you can tell us in the comment section, we will
make a video on that and give it to you, so
this was the complete video of this, I
doubt that whatever dialogues
regarding insurance have been cleared, we will meet you
in the next video, till then
Satyam Gupta signing of sand